[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
[Live Forever]
[Episode 4]
What are you doing here?
Where is your curator?
Curator Lin isn't here.
He went out.
You're new here?
Director Song comes here every month.
After you.
You can't go in.
Do you have an appointment?
You can't enter without appointment.
That batch of Ming Dynasty paintings
needs to be sent to the provincial office for approval by 8 tomorrow.
If we don't finish reviewing them today,
and the higher-ups hold us accountable,
are you going to take the blame,
or am I?
Ning,
how did you communicate with them?
I'm sorry, Director.
So inefficient.
We've already called Curator Lin.
[ID Badge]
You're Zhao, right?
He said you should show us right in.
Oh, you've called him?
Look, I didn't know.
Go on in.
I'm not going.
I'm not going, okay?
Business first. Let's go.
How could I let you carry my bag?
What would that look like?
You carry it.
- Right this way. - Yes, Director.
Take your time.
Awesome!
I didn't know you could do this.
You're not so bad yourself.
You just won't leave me alone, will you?
A good dog doesn't block the way.
I've searched everywhere inside.
Nothing is there.
Let's just go home.
Let's go.
- What if someone sees us later? - What are you doing?
Newspapers! Newspapers!
Excuse me, make way.
Excuse me, coming through.
Save the nation.
Restore our homeland.
This is a time of critical peril.
May our compatriots awaken together.
If our homeland falls,
who can remain unscathed?
Since we were born in this era,
we must do something.
Commander,
we've brought Miss Song back.
You're back.
Didn't you send people to follow me
and bring me back with such fanfare?
Now you're acting like you don't remember?
It's not safe outside these days.
The students are protesting.
It's safer to stay at home.
But the newspaper office hasn't
sent anyone to pick up the drafts for a long time.
If I don't deliver them now, it'll be too late.
The person from the newspaper office
who delivered your drafts was killed.
The content of your newspaper has angered certain people.
If this continues, you'll be in danger too.
Killed?
He was only nineteen.
Who couldn't tolerate
a nineteen-year-old kid?
Was it the police,
the Green Gang,
or you people in high positions?
Qiu...
Commander,
there's an emergency.
I'll be back later.
I must send these drawings out.
I will deliver them myself.
[Song Baiwei]
Commander,
the situation is deteriorating again.
The higher-ups say we must take action.
Find someone
to specifically help Miss Song
deliver her drawings to the newspaper from now on.
Yes, sir.
Save the nation!
Revitalize China!
Strengthen ourselves to save the country!
Save the nation!
-Fall back! -Strengthen ourselves to save the country!
Revitalize China!
Fall back, hurry!
Fall back! What are you doing?
What are you doing?
Trying to rebel?
Why are you arresting us?
You damn traitors!
Go back!
Get in!
Little girl,
go home quickly. It's too dangerous here.
What are you talking about?
Follow me.
Search over there.
Hurry!
It should be safe now.
I'm not very familiar with this area.
But why didn't you...
Doesn't it hurt?
I...
I'm sorry.
I thought you were a member of our student association,
being chased by those bad guys too.
You're from the student association?
Yes.
I'm Lin Huai, the president
of the National Salvation Student Association,
Have we...
met somewhere before?
Hey,
your way of hitting on girls
is too old-fashioned.
I'm serious, I...
Instead of spending time hitting on girls,
you'd better bandage your wound first.
Here.
Let me do it.
Your hand.
Turn it over.
Thank you.
Do you know how many people
have a problem with your student association?
And you're still shouting that
you're the president.
Do you have a death wish?
I really feel like we've met before.
Okay, okay.
We've met.
We met thousands of years ago.
Are you satisfied now?
Thanks for helping me today.
But it's not safe outside right now.
You should hurry back to school.
There's a sniper!
Go!
Don't poke your head out.
They'll come after you again since they failed.
Run!
No.
I'm not leaving.
We leave together.
I'll take you to the hospital.
I won't die.
Just go!
Go!
Let go!
Are you
here for a tour?
Yes, just passing by.
Have we...
met somewhere before?
My name is Lin Huai.
I'm the curator of this art gallery.
Nice to meet you.
Didn't we just meet yesterday, Curator Lin?
This is Song Yiqiu,
my wife.
Ex-wife.
Just divorced.
She's a bit emotional.
You know how it is.
I understand.
Lin Huai.
Curator,
sorry for the abrupt intrusion.
We are also enthusiasts of famous painting research.
We heard your gallery has a rich collection.
We're very curious.
I wonder
if you could give us a tour?
Do you have any collections similar to
Autumn Moon in the Forest?
Because we are
especially, you know...
Obsessed with these paintings.
Yes, yes.
Since you like them,
of course.
Let's go then.
This way.
This is our core collection area.
These paintings...
Look at this one.
This painting is from the Southern Qin dynasty.
It's the first one I ever collected.
♪ So here is to you ♪
♪ My darling ♪
♪ And here is to you, my friend ♪
♪ Here is to you, my lover ♪
Over there are oil paintings from the Republic of China era.
Come here.
♪ I'll follow you until the end ♪
Beautiful, isn't it?
♪ So when the fire are burning ♪
♪ And when the light fades away ♪
From the Southern Qin to the Republic of China,
these paintings cover a huge period of time.
And their styles
can be said to vary drastically.
♪ When the sky is falling ♪
I've been criticized by many people because of this.
They say my art collection
lacks any logic.
♪ I'll never let you be alone ♪
Do you also find it strange?
What is my principle for collecting paintings?
Actually, it's very simple.
I just like them.
Look at these paintings.
These paintings
have no signatures,
no prominent origins.
If put on the art market,
they might even be completely worthless.
♪ So here is to you ♪
♪ My darling ♪
♪ And here is to you ♪
But whenever I look at them,
♪ My friend ♪
I just feel like
the souls behind these paintings,
♪ Here is to you, my lover ♪
no matter how much time has passed,
or how many names they've taken,
seem to be the same person all along.
♪ I'll follow you until the end ♪
Someone
I love deeply.